

Contact information

Email

juananmgz@gmail.com

Address

- Salamanca
- Madrid

Telephone

(+34) 658 01 61 21

Nacionality

Spanish (Española)

Links

- juananmgz.github.io
- linkedin.com/in/juananmgz

Competences

Social skills

Quick learning

Commitment Agile

development

Strategy

Initiative

Leadership

Organization

Performance

Daniel and the first

Responsibility

Teamwork

Languages

Spanish: Native

English: Intermediate Level

More info

Driving Licenseown **Car**

Juan Antonio Muñoz Gómez

FullStack & DevOps Developer | Frontend Designer

Specialized in **Web Development** and **Agile Methodologies**. My goal is to offer users the best product applying my knowledge and experience. My preferences are **Interfaz Design and User Experience (UI & UX)** based on **Human-Computer Interaction**.

Experience

Madrid, Spain

Apr 2022 - Currently

Salamanca, Spain Feb 2021 - Jul 2021

- Curricular Internships: Web Applications Design Monobo
- Curricular Internships: Web Applications and Electronics Design

ESALab Research Group

Education

Alcalá de Henares, Spain 2021 - Currently

Salamanca, España 2017 - 2021 Master in Agile Software Web Development
 University de Alcalá de Henares

Degree in Computer Engineering
 University de Salamanca
 10.0 Honour Mention - Final Degree Project

Formative Courses & Certificates

- BEM CSS + ITCSS = BEMIT Methodology Advanced Web Design. Udemy (2022)
- Scrum Master: Agile project management with Scrum. Viewnext (2021)
- Business and Marketing Plan. Industrial and Intellectual Property. Operations and Human Resources Plan. Fund. General USAL - Plan TCUE (2021)
- · Ionic React: Cross-Platform Mobile Development with Ionic 5. Udemy ESALab (2021)

Other Formative Experiences

- English Native Language Immersion. Edinburgh (2014)
- Musical education [17+ years]. Different associations & instructors (2003-Currently)

Competencies

WEB DEVELOPMENT

- Basic Languages: HTML, CSS, JS, TS, JSON, YAML, PHP, Java, XML
- Frontend: NodeJS, Bootstrap, SASS, JQuery, Angular, VueJS, React, EJS

L. Inmersive Frontend: (3D) Spline, WebGL / (Animations) Efectos Parallax, SVG

DevOps & CI/CD: Docker, Kubernetes, Istio, JUnit, Maven, Selenium, SonarQube, Heroku
 BackEnd: Express, Spring + Eureka, Servlets, JPA, APIs REST, Perl / Apache, NGinx

• UX & Prototyping: Adobe XD, MockUp, WireFrame, Heuristicas, IPO/IPM, C.R.A.P.

WORKING METHODOLOGIES

- Scrum + Kanban + Lean + XP: Scrum Master. Jira, Taiga, Mic. Project
- **BEMIT:** BEM + ITCSS
- Version Control: Git → GitHub, GitLab (+ DevOps Method.)

Awards & Recognisements

- ICE 2021 Business Project Cultural Entrepreneurship Discipline, FUESCyL (2022)
- TCUE Market Oriented Prototypes Grant, Fund. General USAL (2021)
- Traditional Music Award Young Talent, Arlafolk (2019)

Articles

Available at orcid.com: 0000-0001-6794-5445